<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<TED_EXPORT xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink"
            xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
            xmlns="http://publications.europa.eu/resource/schema/ted/R2.0.9/publication"
            xmlns:n2016="http://publications.europa.eu/resource/schema/ted/2016/nuts"
            xsi:schemaLocation="http://publications.europa.eu/resource/schema/ted/R2.0.9/publication TED_EXPORT.xsd"
            VERSION="R2.0.9.S03.E01"
            DOC_ID="255409-2020"
            EDITION="2020105">
   <TECHNICAL_SECTION>
      <RECEPTION_ID>20-260117-001</RECEPTION_ID>
      <DELETION_DATE>20200613</DELETION_DATE>
      <FORM_LG_LIST>EN </FORM_LG_LIST>
      <COMMENTS>From Convertor</COMMENTS>
   </TECHNICAL_SECTION>
   <LINKS_SECTION>
      <XML_SCHEMA_DEFINITION_LINK xlink:type="simple"
                                  xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"
                                  xlink:title="TED WEBSITE"/>
      <OFFICIAL_FORMS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/>
      <FORMS_LABELS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/>
      <ORIGINAL_CPV_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/>
      <ORIGINAL_NUTS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/>
   </LINKS_SECTION>
   <CODED_DATA_SECTION>
      <REF_OJS>
         <COLL_OJ>S</COLL_OJ>
         <NO_OJ>105</NO_OJ>
         <DATE_PUB>20200602</DATE_PUB>
      </REF_OJS>
      <NOTICE_DATA>
         <NO_DOC_OJS>2020/S 105-255409</NO_DOC_OJS>
         <URI_LIST>
            <URI_DOC LG="EN">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:255409-2020:TEXT:EN:HTML</URI_DOC>
         </URI_LIST>
         <LG_ORIG>EN</LG_ORIG>
         <ISO_COUNTRY VALUE="KE"/>
         <IA_URL_GENERAL>www.fsdkenya.org</IA_URL_GENERAL>
         <IA_URL_ETENDERING>https://fsdkenya.org/about-us/opportunities/</IA_URL_ETENDERING>
         <ORIGINAL_CPV CODE="66170000">Financial consultancy, financial transaction processing and clearing-house services</ORIGINAL_CPV>
         <n2016:PERFORMANCE_NUTS CODE="00">Not specified / Other</n2016:PERFORMANCE_NUTS>
         <n2016:CA_CE_NUTS CODE="00">Not specified / Other</n2016:CA_CE_NUTS>
      </NOTICE_DATA>
      <CODIF_DATA>
         <DS_DATE_DISPATCH>20200528</DS_DATE_DISPATCH>
         <DT_DATE_FOR_SUBMISSION>20200612 16:00</DT_DATE_FOR_SUBMISSION>
         <AA_AUTHORITY_TYPE CODE="8">Other</AA_AUTHORITY_TYPE>
         <TD_DOCUMENT_TYPE CODE="3">Contract notice</TD_DOCUMENT_TYPE>
         <NC_CONTRACT_NATURE CODE="4">Services</NC_CONTRACT_NATURE>
         <PR_PROC CODE="1">Open procedure</PR_PROC>
         <RP_REGULATION CODE="Z">Not specified</RP_REGULATION>
         <TY_TYPE_BID CODE="1">Submission for all lots</TY_TYPE_BID>
         <AC_AWARD_CRIT CODE="2">The most economic tender</AC_AWARD_CRIT>
         <MA_MAIN_ACTIVITIES CODE="8">Other</MA_MAIN_ACTIVITIES>
         <HEADING>08C02</HEADING>
         <INITIATOR>08</INITIATOR>
      </CODIF_DATA>
   </CODED_DATA_SECTION>
   <TRANSLATION_SECTION>
      <ML_TITLES>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="BG">
            <TI_CY>Кения</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Найроби</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Финансови консултантски услуги, финансови транзакции и услуги на клирингови къщи</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="CS">
            <TI_CY>Keňa</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Nairobi</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Finanční poradenství, zpracování finančních transakcí a služby zúčtovacího střediska</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="DA">
            <TI_CY>Kenya</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Nairobi</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Finansielle konsulentydelser, behandling og clearing af finansielle transaktioner</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="DE">
            <TI_CY>Kenia</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Nairobi</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Finanzberatung, Bearbeitung und Clearing von Finanzgeschäften</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="EL">
            <TI_CY>Κένυα</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Ναϊρόμπι</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Υπηρεσίες παροχής οικονομικών συμβουλών, επεξεργασίας χρηματοπιστωτικών συναλλαγών και γραφείων συμψηφισμού</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="EN">
            <TI_CY>Kenya</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Nairobi</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Financial consultancy, financial transaction processing and clearing-house services</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="ES">
            <TI_CY>Kenia</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Nairobi</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Servicios de asesoramiento financiero, de procesamiento de transacciones financieras y de cámara de compensación</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="ET">
            <TI_CY>Kenya</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Nairobi</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Finantskonsultatsiooni-, finantstehingute käitlemis- ja arvelduskoja teenused</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="FI">
            <TI_CY>Kenia</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Nairobi</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Rahoitusneuvonta, rahoitustapahtumien käsittely- ja selvitysyhtiöpalvelut</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="FR">
            <TI_CY>Kenya</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Nairobi</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Services de conseils financiers, services de traitement des transactions financières et services de chambres de compensation</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="GA">
            <TI_CY>Chéinia, an</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Nairobi</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Financial consultancy, financial transaction processing and clearing-house services</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="HR">
            <TI_CY>Kenija</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Nairobi</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Usluge financijskog savjetovanja, obrade financijskih transakcija i usluge klirinških organizacija</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="HU">
            <TI_CY>Kenya</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Nairobi</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Pénzügyi tanácsadó, tranzakció-feldolgozási és klíringintézeti szolgáltatások</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="IT">
            <TI_CY>Kenya (Kenia)</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Nairobi</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Servizi di consulenza finanziaria, di gestione delle transazioni finanziarie e di compensazione</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="LT">
            <TI_CY>Kenija</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Nairobis</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Finansinės konsultacijos, finansinių sandorių apdorojimas ir kliringo namų paslaugos</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="LV">
            <TI_CY>Kenija</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Nairobi</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Finanšu konsultāciju, finanšu darījumu apstrādes un ieskaita sabiedrību pakalpojumi</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="MT">
            <TI_CY>il-Kenja</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Nairobi</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Servizzi ta' konsulenza finanzjarja, ta' proċessar ta' tranżazzjonijiet finanzjarji u ta' clearing-house</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="NL">
            <TI_CY>Kenia</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Nairobi</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Diensten op het gebied van financiële consultancy, financiële transacties en clearing</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="PL">
            <TI_CY>Kenia</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Nairobi</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Usługi w zakresie doradztwa finansowego, przetwarzania transakcji finansowych i usługi izb rozrachunkowych</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="PT">
            <TI_CY>Quénia</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Nairobi</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Serviços de consultoria financeira, de processamento de transacções financeiras e das câmaras de compensação</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="RO">
            <TI_CY>Kenya</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Nairobi</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Servicii de consultanţă financiară, de gestionare a tranzacţiilor financiare şi servicii de case de compensare</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="SK">
            <TI_CY>Keňa</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Nairobi</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Služby týkajúce finančného poradenstva, spracovania finančných transakcií a klíringových ústavov</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="SL">
            <TI_CY>Kenija</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Nairobi</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Storitve finančnega svetovanja, obdelave in kliringa finančnih transakcij</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="SV">
            <TI_CY>Kenya</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Nairobi</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Finansiell rådgivning, hantering av finansiella transaktioner och clearinghouse-tjänster</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
      </ML_TITLES>
      <ML_AA_NAMES>
         <AA_NAME LG="EN">Financial Sector Deepening Trust (Kenya)</AA_NAME>
      </ML_AA_NAMES>
   </TRANSLATION_SECTION>
   <FORM_SECTION>
      <F02_2014 CATEGORY="ORIGINAL" FORM="F02" LG="EN">
         <LEGAL_BASIS VALUE="32014L0024"/>
         <CONTRACTING_BODY>
            <ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY>
               <OFFICIALNAME>Financial Sector Deepening Trust (Kenya)</OFFICIALNAME>
               <ADDRESS>Box 11353</ADDRESS>
               <TOWN>Nairobi</TOWN>
               <POSTAL_CODE>00100</POSTAL_CODE>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="KE"/>
               <CONTACT_POINT>Lydiah Kioko</CONTACT_POINT>
               <PHONE>+254 205137300</PHONE>
               <E_MAIL>tenders@fsdkenya.org</E_MAIL>
               <n2016:NUTS CODE="00"/>
               <URL_GENERAL>www.fsdkenya.org</URL_GENERAL>
            </ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY>
            <DOCUMENT_FULL/>
            <URL_DOCUMENT>https://fsdkenya.org/about-us/opportunities/</URL_DOCUMENT>
            <ADDRESS_FURTHER_INFO_IDEM/>
            <ADDRESS_PARTICIPATION_IDEM/>
            <CA_TYPE_OTHER>Donor agency using funds from EU member states (United Kingdom and the Government of Sweden)</CA_TYPE_OTHER>
            <CA_ACTIVITY_OTHER>International development</CA_ACTIVITY_OTHER>
         </CONTRACTING_BODY>
         <OBJECT_CONTRACT>
            <TITLE>
               <P>Government of Kenya Collections Strategy</P>
            </TITLE>
            <CPV_MAIN>
               <CPV_CODE CODE="66170000"/>
            </CPV_MAIN>
            <TYPE_CONTRACT CTYPE="SERVICES"/>
            <SHORT_DESCR>
               <P>Governments are the largest payer and receiver of cash in any economy and Kenya is no exception. It is estimated that GoK represents 60 % of payments and collections in the economy. Following a presidential directive to digitise all government collections in the country which would effectively eliminate cash from Government offices a Government Digital Payments (GDP) task force was set up to oversee the implementation of this key project which saw the deployment of e-Citizen, a single sign-on platform that allows citizens to access, apply and pay for government services. To date about three hundred out of a possible five thousand government services have been fully digitised and the revenue collected through the platform has been growing steadily since 2015. Currently, over eight million citizens are registered on the e-citizen platform.</P>
            </SHORT_DESCR>
            <NO_LOT_DIVISION/>
            <OBJECT_DESCR ITEM="1">
               <n2016:NUTS CODE="00"/>
               <SHORT_DESCR>
                  <P>In 2019, FSD Kenya re-engaged with the GDP team which continues to work to digitise the remaining government services. FSD Kenya initially supported the development of a proof of concept, securing the platform against cyber-attacks as well as development of an agency model that would efficiently implement this initiative. Based on recommendations from the first phase, it was agreed that FSD Kenya would continue to support the GDP team to undertake a market analysis, a legal and regulatory review and the development of a strategy and business case. Work on the first two activities is going on although has recently slowed due to effects of Covid-19. FSD Kenya is now looking for a consultancy firm or team of consultants to support the GDP in developing the strategy. The work will focus on the following key areas:</P>
                  <P>— identify the key strategic objectives and key indicators for success;</P>
                  <P>— develop a business case for GDP including costs and benefits to be accrued on full digitization of government collections. This will include the necessary incentives to drive the implementation of the strategy;</P>
                  <P>— a detailed implementation plan including sustainability options such as private and public management of the platform and onboarding of remaining services on the platform.</P>
               </SHORT_DESCR>
               <AC>
                  <AC_PROCUREMENT_DOC/>
               </AC>
               <DATE_START>2020-07-20</DATE_START>
               <DATE_END>2020-11-30</DATE_END>
               <RENEWAL/>
               <RENEWAL_DESCR>
                  <P>The contract will be renewed in the event of delays occasioned by exogenous factors.</P>
               </RENEWAL_DESCR>
               <NO_ACCEPTED_VARIANTS/>
               <NO_OPTIONS/>
               <EU_PROGR_RELATED>
                  <P>Funded by funds from EU member countries — UK Department for International Development and the Government of Sweden.</P>
               </EU_PROGR_RELATED>
            </OBJECT_DESCR>
         </OBJECT_CONTRACT>
         <LEFTI>
            <TECHNICAL_PROFESSIONAL_INFO>
               <P>The consulting firm or team of consultants should have:</P>
               <P>— strong understanding of government collections landscape in Kenya and globally;</P>
               <P>— demonstrable deep knowledge and understanding of the global payments market with a bias on government payments;</P>
               <P>— reputation, market position and record of implementing similar assignments;</P>
               <P>— relevant technical and commercial skills;</P>
               <P>— ability to work flexibly, including availability on short notice.</P>
            </TECHNICAL_PROFESSIONAL_INFO>
            <TECHNICAL_PROFESSIONAL_MIN_LEVEL>
               <P>Expressions of interest must include a capability statement, of no more than four (4) A4 pages, which shows evidence of relevant skills and experience in providing the services required under this contract notice. Abridged CVs of key personnel only, each of not more than three (3) pages in length, should also be included. These CVs can be submitted in addition to the four page capability statement. Expressions of interest should be submitted preferably by email to tenders@fsdkenya.org (reference: Government Collection Strategy). Following assessment of expressions of interest, FSD Kenya will invite short-listed applicants to submit full technical and commercial proposals.</P>
            </TECHNICAL_PROFESSIONAL_MIN_LEVEL>
         </LEFTI>
         <PROCEDURE>
            <PT_OPEN/>
            <ACCELERATED_PROC>
               <P>Two distinct workstreams whose findings are critical to its development are currently underway and timetabled for completion in July. These are:</P>
               <P>(a) a landscape review which will provide a detailed analysis of the implementation of different government collection initiatives in Kenya;</P>
               <P>(b) the legal and regulatory review which will provide an analysis of the legislative and regulatory framework currently in place to support the successful implementation of the programme.</P>
               <P>Acceleration of timeline is therefore sought on the basis that:</P>
               <P>(a) the strategy development provider should be identified in advance and undertake the foundational work prior to submission of the two critical pieces so as to keep the momentum going and ensure the work is in alignment with the agreed timelines</P>
               <P>(b) there is a strong desire by the Government of Kenya and other stakeholders to complete the assignment at the earliest to allow for planning and implementation of specific policies in the next fiscal year.</P>
            </ACCELERATED_PROC>
            <NO_CONTRACT_COVERED_GPA/>
            <DATE_RECEIPT_TENDERS>2020-06-12</DATE_RECEIPT_TENDERS>
            <TIME_RECEIPT_TENDERS>16:00</TIME_RECEIPT_TENDERS>
            <LANGUAGES>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="EN"/>
            </LANGUAGES>
            <DURATION_TENDER_VALID TYPE="MONTH">6</DURATION_TENDER_VALID>
            <OPENING_CONDITION>
               <DATE_OPENING_TENDERS>2020-06-15</DATE_OPENING_TENDERS>
               <TIME_OPENING_TENDERS>08:00</TIME_OPENING_TENDERS>
               <PLACE>
                  <P>Nairobi — KENYA.</P>
               </PLACE>
            </OPENING_CONDITION>
         </PROCEDURE>
         <COMPLEMENTARY_INFO>
            <NO_RECURRENT_PROCUREMENT/>
            <ADDRESS_REVIEW_BODY>
               <OFFICIALNAME>Financial Sector Deepening Trust (FSD Kenya)</OFFICIALNAME>
               <ADDRESS>11353</ADDRESS>
               <TOWN>Nairobi</TOWN>
               <POSTAL_CODE>00100</POSTAL_CODE>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="KE"/>
               <PHONE>+254 205137300</PHONE>
               <E_MAIL>info@fsdkenya.org</E_MAIL>
            </ADDRESS_REVIEW_BODY>
            <DATE_DISPATCH_NOTICE>2020-05-28</DATE_DISPATCH_NOTICE>
         </COMPLEMENTARY_INFO>
      </F02_2014>
   </FORM_SECTION>
</TED_EXPORT>
